Mechanical Cat's health diagnoses'
Why is he muddieheaded?
But he is muddleheaded every time.
Mechanical Cat, irksome, what should I
do?
What's matter with you?
You have been teased by Giant again?
No.
So?
Test, I will test tomorrow.
Test, it is exaggerated.
It is fine that you study now.
It is too late now.
I forgot what I studied.
I will test tomorrow.
It is useless that you just studied one
day.
I don't want to get zero.
Dore...
Gees, I have been laughed.
You look,
to take light pen out.
To take light pen out, I could get full
mark.
Can't.
You should depend on yourself.
I have studied hard already.
My study time is up every day.
I have tried my best.
It isn't enough.
You should keep on studying hard.
But I will test tomorrow.
It is late now.
So please,
give me light pen.
Nobita
Sit down.
I asked you to sit down.
No, you don't give me light pen,
I don't sit well.
Nobita
I don't want... I don't do it if you don't
give me.
You...
Anyway, I can't.
You are brutal, you lie there.
Please.
You ever gave me before.
I will study by myself next time.
Hurry to help me.
Mechanical Cat
Hello,
What's matter with you, Mechanical Cat?
You cheer up.
I just a bit swirl.
Sorry, Mechanical Cat
I shouldn't jump on you.
You look,
it is Dorami.
Gees.
Nobita, it isn't your fault.
Dorami, you came.
What? I again?
I am also busy.
Because you don't go to factory.
Factory?
We robot should go back factory
and check health yearly.
But brother don't go always.
I am fine.
Why did you faint?
Because...
So...
Mechanical Cat
Shit, some strange sound.
You will die if you don't check again.
Shit, I am fine, you are wordy.
Don't care me.
Mechanical Cat, brother.
Brother is stubborn.
Why didn't he want to go?
He must be afraid.
What should you do if you have some
trouble?
Trouble?
Yes, such as paroxysm amnesia.
Paroxysm amnesia?
You will forget anything quickly.
Or bad direction-sense.
Direction-sense?
But the most troublesome is part
failure.
Part failure?
It will break forever if you don't cure
hurry.
Impotent.
Yes, so you must be hurry up.
OK, I must ask him to go to factory.
Thank you.
So, Nobita, please.
Where?
Mechanical Cat
Shit, why didn't he cherish his body,
he is stubborn.
Mechanical Cat...
Mechanical Cat
It is really napoo this time.
Strange.
The secondhand car has been used for
ten years.
It is useless that you repair it,
you should buy another cheap.
Mechanical Cat...
Nobita, I am really fine.
And, if I is in hospital for more one
year,
who takes care of Nobita?
He doesn't know doing anything.
I am tired, let's me sleep.
Nobita doesn't know if he can persuade
brother,
if he can't...
Mouse...
No, there are mouse.
Eat it...
Mechanical Cat
What's matter?
Did you have a nightmare?
You cried loud.
Dream, it is vivid.
Done.
But I am lucky that brother thought he
dreamed.
Because your body have something
wrong, so you had a nightmare.
You must go to factory hurry.
Don't have a finger in the pie.
I worry you, but you think
I have a finger in the pie.
You are so stubborn.
Look, something wrong.
Nothing.
You should be worried about.
If I am not here, how will you live?
I see, you worry me.
Please, just because of it,
Even Mechanical Cat isn't here,
I am also... fine.
Sure?
Yes.
Okay, if I get full mark tomorrow,
you go to factory at once.
Full mark?
No, 90 mark.
No, 80 mark.
If I get mark of 70, you go to factory.
If you get mark of 60, I will go to
factory.
But you can't do it.
So, let me try.
What is it?
But for Mechanical Cat,
I must study hard.
But the mouse was really dream?
I feel strange.
Mechanical Cat
How come?
Treasure in the pocket...
Something is moving in my stomach?
Could it be... mouse?
But it does not include that mouse
ran into my mouth.
Impossible.
Maybe it is machine bug.
But something is really in my stomach.
You cheer up.
Well,
Nobita...
What are you doing?
Could it be...
No, no.
Transform small light'
Sterilization Light Gun'
Mechanical Cat, give me it.
I transform small with it and enter
your body
And kill bug for you.
No, if you touch high tension line
what should I do?
If you drop into atomic bag, you will
be destroyed and become energy sources.
If you drop into vitta...
Don't delay.
Can't.
Wait for me, Mechanical Cat,
Mechanical Cat...
Nobita
Lucky, it is soft, it hasn't been hurt.
But what is this?
As if it is rug.
It is Rice Cracker.
So here is stomach.
Mechanical Cat, gees, glut.
And didn't bite at all.
You are edacious.
Could it be you haven't digested?
Something is moving.
Maybe it is machine bug.
Mini-Dore
Mechanical Cat, don't move suddenly.
Mini-Dore, why are you here?
Times TV
This is Dorami.
This is detector.
It could help you to check failure.
You turn off switch as soon as it
enter your stomach.
Don't forget.
Please, Mini-Dore.
To enter brother's body, if something
wrong...
You repair him.
Cheer up.
That's it.
Mechanical Cat, what's matter with you?
This is Dorami.
I see.
The goods Mechanical Cat swallowed
down isn't mouse, it is Mini-Dore.
How come?
One man can't finish it, Nobita
and baby Mini-Dore.
You entered my body actually.
Mechanical Cat is troublesome.
This is...
... a detector Dorami gave you.
It can check failure.
It is near treasure pocket.
Mechanical Cat, she has know where is
wrong.
She will repair it for you at once.
Here is a short cut.
It is oil.
Its speed is fast.
I tell you that I don't know swimming
at all.
I see.
No batteries.
What's matter with Nobita?
Help.
Nobita
I drop in vitta.
So I think it is dangerous.
Mini-Dore, to take it out.
That, just that!
Just that!
When you meet a person who fell into
water, give him one piece of swim straw.
Then he'll be able to swim.
In spite of going up or down.
Fortunately Mini-Dore has a piece of
swim straw on him.
Nobita, it's too dangerous,
come back right now!
No, I'll cure you by all means.
Stained with oil all over,
it makes me sick!
What's this...
Nobita
Help, many electric balls are tracing
me!
That's the electric balls!
They'll decompose the abnormal
molecules in you body.
Don't move, keeping this,
it's very hard to run!
Nobita, hurry to run, hurry up!
I want to go home quickly.
At this time you want me to play
baseball!
I've played for so long, but no one hit!
I was saved!
What's the matter?
Found it, just here!
Mechanical Cat,
I found your failure reason finally.
Why was it frozen?
Frozen?
Can't it be that the liquid leaked out?
Let me repair you right away!
I don't expect you can do it at all.
Hurry to come back!
I have a bad forefeeling.
That's okay, so simple.
Mechanical Cat, I repaired it,
you're all right!
You can still live for a long time...
What's this?
It's almost engulfed!
It's almost engulfed? What's it?
Can't it be...the failure part is
beside the bag.
It's almost engulfed?
Can't it be the omnipotent bag?
Mechanical Cat
Nobita, you mustn't be engulfed!
I don't want either!
Sometimes even I can't find out
the properties in my bag
If you're engulfed,
maybe I won't find you out for ever!
Nobita...
Do your best, Nobita!
You must do your best.
I'll do something too.
I also hope I could!
Nobita
Mechanical Cat
Nobita...
Nobita...Nobita
I wonder whether Nobita has persuaded
brother.
Nobita! Brother!
Nobita, he...
Brother, what's your problem?
Nobita he...
What's wrong with Nobita?
He's in the bag...
Nobita he...
Mechanical Cat
Mechanical Cat, I'm here!
Nobita
Nobita! Mechanical Cat!
I see, it's been hard on youl!
After all how did you get saved?
I thought I would be doomed to die!
Just at the moment that I let go, ...
As a result I got out of it
by the umbrella hook.
And helped you to bind up your wound.
So it is, great!
It causes me to live less for 10 years.
Brother!
This is a reservation car for repairing.
You must go to the factory to
repair the failure part.
I will.
If such thing happens again, it's
no use how long your life is.
So brother, take care!
I'll wait you over there.
Thank you, Mini-Dore, Dorami...
Good bye!
All right!
I'll go on studying.
I should let you set your heart at rest,
then go to have a physical examination.
If only you're willing to do,
there will be no problem!
I got over even the difficulty just now.
Yes, that's it.
My goal is a mark of 60!
How terrible!
I'm very serious!